Cinderella
Cinderella's Sister
So it's my house in May 2020 right now?
Around then, we have to bring Mom over to live next to us.
Hyo Seon should also be married by then.
Mom won't have anyone to torment, so she'll feel empty inside.
We'll bring her over, and let her annoy us.
It'll take around ten years to buy a house.
We should be able to do it if we tighten our belts.
You feel uneasy right now, don't you?
All you can think about is your dad, right?
I thought that would be the case, so I wanted to calm you down before letting you go.
I feel peaceful now.
Is that so?
This...has given me strength.
- Really?
- Yes, like a big army to my rescue.
If you go back on your words in the future... you know the consequences.
Your father will be all over the news and newspapers.
I know.
Hyo Seon will also find out soon.
Right. I'll tell her before she finds out.
I kept missing my chances to tell her like I did with you. I can't let her find out from someone else.
Do you know what?
I was always afraid of the things I had to deal with.
Now, I'm not afraid of anything.
- Really?
- Really.
I can handle it well. I'll get through it.
Whether it's about my dad or Hong Joo Ga,
and even telling Hyo Seon. I'll get through it all.
Let's go. Let's go reveal who I am to Hyo Seon.
Ahjusshis, I know you've worked hard all this time.
Seeing how things aren't doing so great right now, I've prepared these hiking outfits for each of you,
so we can go hiking together. But wait and see.
I seem like someone who doesn't know gratitude, right?
But if I set my mind to repay my gratitude, I'll definitely do it.
Just watch and see what the owner of Dae Seong True Winemakers is like.
Just work hard as you have been doing. Just like you're doing now.
Understand?
Hurry and get back to work.
Uncle, Mom says she wants to see you.
Hyo Seon, can you tell me what she wants to say ahead of time?
You see, she and I, you see...
it's a bit... you know... for us to see each other face to face.
It's okay, Uncle. It's okay.
Just hurry and go.
Aigoo. Hyo Seon, this is...
Don't worry. Go in, Uncle.
Remember, I've got your back.
Just trust me and go in.
A-All right, Hyo Seon.
I...You grew up riding on my back. You remember that, right?
You never wanted to get off of my back.
I'm a little hunchbacked because of that!
Don't worry and go see Mom, Uncle.
All right.
Hyo Seon.
Although we live in one house, it's been a while since we last saw each other.
You're right.
You guys came back together?
There's something I want to tell you.
Let's go in.
Mr. Hong Gi Hoon.
(Prosecutor's Badge)
- You're aware that Hong Joo Ga's Chairman Hong Han Seok is being investigated by the prosecutor's office, right?
- Yes.
It's been discovered that there's a slush fund of a huge amount deposited in your bank account.
I think you need to come with us.
What did you say?
- I'll be back.
- What happened?
Where...where are you going?
I'm not sure if it will be long or not, but I'll be back.
Don't worry and just wait for me.
What is it? Who are those people?
I told you I'll handle things well.
It seems there's something else I have to handle now.
It's okay, I can handle it.
Who are those people?
Excuse me.
They're prosecutors.
I said I'll handle it. It's all right.
Help me tell Hyo Seon.
Tell her everything from the beginning.
Don't hide anything and tell her everything.
Please do it for me.
What are you saying?
Hide what? What are you asking her to do?
What did prosecutors come to find you?
I'll be back.
Wait!
Wait! Wait a moment!
Open the door! I have something to say!
Open the door!
Why aren't you coming in? Do I need to come out?
Sit.
I'm...fine here.
Just sit! How many times do I have to ask?
You know I don't even want to see your face at all, right?
I'm asking you a question, so respond!
Y-Yes... I know.
You also probably feel the same as me.
You don't want to see me even for a moment, right?
That...that's right, yes.
Even though I want to kick you out right away, that brat, Hyo Seon will make a fuss again.
Then she'll bother the elders and make it into a big problem.
Look here, Uncle.
Where should I look?
The most peaceful way for us to go our separate ways
is for you to get married.
No...but...I need to have a girlfriend for that to happen...
Even if I have a girlfriend, I need to have money or some assets...
Even if I do...the girl...
No...so...it's impossible for that to happen in a short time...
This is my old friend's distant relative. Try meeting her.
I... If I leave this place, I have nowhere to go.
I don't have any savings, and I've really got nothing to my name.
And I wouldn't know how to make a living in the city.
So I'm pleading for forgiveness.
I've really reflected on myself.
Just look at the picture!
Okay...
If I just send you away with nothing, Hyo Seon will cause a commotion,
and even if not her,
I can't ignore how much Hyo Seon's father thought of you so
I can give you what you need to start off,
but after that, don't even expect a single thing from this family.
If you have a conscience, you'll understand that, right?
I can't believe it.
Oppa Gi Hoon did that?
Oppa Gi Hoon headed the plan to ruin Dad?
Are you asking me to believe that?
You're seriously asking me to believe you?
What is with you guys?
What are you guys plotting?
I...have a headache, Hyo Seon.
Don't be agitated. There's still more I have to say.
You...You're trying to take revenge on me, aren't you?
Because I didn't give you that letter and hid it from you,
so now you're trying to take revenge on me, right?
You think I'll get hurt
if you denigrate the man I've always liked, don't you?
You want to humiliate me for being attracted to the man
who tried to ruin my dad, right?
I can't stand it!
I really can't stand someone like you!
How in the world did I spend the last eight years
begging and crying for your love?
I feel wronged.
How can you ... how can you do this to me
for a mistake of hiding one measly letter?
Hyo Seon.
Do you know how my life changed ever since you appeared?
Dad had all his attention on you, and only had eyes for you,
so I had to share my dad with you.
On top of that, suddenly, for some unknown reason,
I can no longer see my dad now.
I even found out that Mom's love for me was fake,
and that Mom betrayed Dad.
Because I still couldn't give up even a mother like that,
I could only cry pathetically.
And finally, because I'm only a stepdaughter,
when I was told that I can be treated only as well as a stepdaughter, I had to act grateful.
But now, it's Oppa Gi Hoon?
Oppa did what?
What did he do?
Hyo Seon.
Don't touch me.
Hyo Seon!
I'm asking within the things you've lost at home, is there something you've never been able to find?
Since you're mine, you can't get married to anyone. Okay?
My heart is thumping, Oppa.
♫ when I wake up from an exhausted sleep  ♫
Let's send Ahjusshi off properly.
♫ because I still remember you smiling ♫
Hyo Seon!
Hyo Seon, are you okay?
Hyo Seon! Hyo Seon!
- Let go!
- Hyo Seon.
Don't touch me!
Hyo Seon!
♫ I walk this street again ♫
It's okay. It's okay.
♫ I am living day after day  ♫
♫ In your name when tears appear, ah ♫
♫ I can't bear it ♫
♫ So I can't laugh ♫
♫ I'll call out your name again ♫
There's still more I have to tell you.
I've thought hard about whether it's right to tell you, or if I should tell you later.
But I think it's better to feel the pain all at once.
That person...and I...
Unni...
Oppa Gi Hoon...
is so pitiful.
I want to give him a hug.
When Dad first brought Gi Hoon here,
he said he was someone he wanted to take care of.
He's someone that shines like a jade,
but he's becoming fragile like glass,
We have to take care of him so he doesn't break,
so help me do that too, Hyo Seon.
That's what Dad said.
If he hadn't left and stayed with Dad the whole time,
he wouldn't have shattered.
How many pieces
did he shatter into?
Our Oppa Gi Hoon...
If I said I'll put the pieces together for him,
would he let me?
Tell him not to run away.
Once he sees my face,
he may not be able to face me,
and run away,
so help me tell him, Unni.
Tell him not to run away.
Are fairytales not suited for me after all?
No, I didn't know.
It's my first time hearing I have such an account.
Every year, there was activity of billions to even ten billions of won in that account. You didn't know at all?
I didn't.
I never even imagined it.
But as an employee of Hong Joo Ga...
Am I not allowed to have a gentle, sweet,
relaxing and beautiful
world of fairytales?
How is my father doing?
Could you let me see him even just for a bit?
It's not like I want to rewrite the rules of the universe
or save the world,
Nor am I trying to save the country...
Hello? Is this Prosecutor Kim Hyeong Man?
I'm Goo Eun Jo, Hong Gi Hoon's friend who called you before.
Is it not possible for me to see him?
Then...when will I be able to see him? Can I not even see him for a little bit?
Wait...Wait a minute.
Wait, please don't hang up.
There's...There's something I have to say to him.
Can you pass a message to him?
I wanted to tell him I am waiting for him.
N-Never mind. Sorry.
There's nothing I want to say. Sorry.
I still haven't been able to call that person's name.
So...I just wanted to live and be able to call his name.
Is it really that wrong?
Song Eun Jo is forever Han Jeong Woo's woman
Try throwing it. I taught you.
Throw with all your might, punk.
One more time.
Come on, one more time.
Your conversation will be recorded and logged.
I understand. Thank you.
Who would've guessed we'd end up meeting here.
Are you okay?
How do I seem?
It must be hard on you.
It's not easy.
Is it harder to hold on than it is to let go, Father?
How are you doing?
It's easy for me.
I just have to say what I know, and tell them I don't know to things I don't know.
Dad.
I want to live with you, Dad.
I really mean it.
There are many times when I wished that you were simply my father.
I know what will happen if you admit everything.
You'll have to go to prison,
and it's hard to predict how long you'll have to spend in there.
In others' eyes, it may seem immoral for a son to ask his father to go to prison,
but I'll wait for you.
I'll wait, along with a pretty brat. We'll take care of you, get a house ready and wait for you.
That brat also promised she would do that.
Don't cling onto anything else other than me, okay?
The elders have decided not to sell their shares to Hong Joo Ga.
They've even gotten back the shares they had already sold.
Really?
I just got the call from them. What happened?
They must've seen the news reports.
I...I feel anxious.
Do you think Oppa Gi Hoon knows this?
If he knows, he'll probably feel less burdened.
Then he'll feel more at ease while being interrogated.
I'm going to go to Seoul to see Oppa Gi Hoon tomorrow morning.
Do you want to come with me?
Can you come with me?
If he sees me first, it'll be hard on him.
Hyo Seon.
What if...
What I'm saying is...I...
What if I only think of myself and just do what I want?
I wanted to ask that.
But...in front of this child that I had taken everything from,
this child that has nothing left of her own,
I held back and couldn't say it.
Okay.
I'll go with you.
Thanks.
Gosh, what is going on with him suddenly?
It's great that I saw you.
Jeong Woo told me to give this to Joon Soo's eldest noona.
Why is that kid, without any notice... without any loyalty... doing something like this all of a sudden?
Aigoo. He just left.
No matter where I am, no matter where Noona is,
you're the only woman in my heart.
No matter what you do, I'll support you.
If you need me, I'll run to you anytime.
Remember this.
Where did he say he's going?
Which way did he go?
Jeong Woo.
Juwon Road
Jeong Woo! Jeong Woo! Jeong Woo!
Don't run! You'll get hurt!
Jeong Woo!
Why do you run like that? You'll all out of breath.
Where are you going? Do you have a place to go?
- Are you leaving because you have somewhere to go?
- Don't worry.
I have lots of places I can go. The only problem is that no one wants me to come.
Stop playing around. Let's go home.
I wanted to do this at least once.
But I didn't dare.
If I release you now, you'll probably hit me.
It's okay. I'll let you hit me before I leave.
Be well.
Thank you for coming to see me off.
I won't starve. Don't worry about me.
If you're not doing well, I'll know right away.
If you need me, I'll come right away.
Make sure you don't make me drop whatever I'm doing and run here right away
so you have to be well, okay?
How can I let you go like this?
I haven't done anything for you yet. Leave some other time.
Let Noona give you a bank account with plenty of earned interest.
And until I'm able to do something for you,
Go then, okay?
You keep it.
If you need it, use it. If you don't, then just keep making it grow.
Wherever I go, I am with you. Got it?
♫ Looking only in this direction ♫
♫ my two eyes ♫
♫ can't say they waited for you  ♫
Jeong Woo!
♫ I can't say I'm coming back  ♫
♫ Will you who knows everthing about me  ♫
♫  who cannot forget you ♫
♫  return to me? ♫
♫  If there are tens of thousand who will just love you ♫
♫  If I can always look at you ♫
♫  The day I return to your side again ♫
I could just leave like that.
It's not something that difficult.
I could just simply leave with a smile, just like Jeong Woo.
You can rely on me.
Lean on me.
You lean on me now, okay?
Incoming call
...
I'm coming home now.
My interrogation is over, and I'm coming to you.
Eun Jo?
Eun Jo. Eun Jo.
Are you listening?
Eun Jo.
Yes. I'm listening.
Why aren't you talking, brat?
I missed hearing your voice so much.
I did well.
I got through it all by thinking of you.
Praise me.
I told you to praise me, you brat. Tell me I did well.
You did well.
I also saw my dad.
I even grabbed his hand.
You did really well.
I grabbed his hand tightly.
Eun Jo.
Yeah?
I want to see you.
Yes.
I'm coming to you now.
Eun Jo.
Yes?
I'm hungry.
Okay.
I'm coming to you now,
my stupid brat.
Please take care of Hyo Seon.
Unni abandoned me and left.
Please tell me, I beg of you.
I don't know.
Have you ever heard of anyone running away and saying where they're going?
Eun Jo and I made a promise.
I can't understand her reason for doing this so suddenly.
You know where Eun Jo went, right?
I...I said I don't know!
Few months later
I already told you. Don't you listen when I speak?
Hey! Mr. Kim! Mr. Kim!
Mr. Kim! You've all worked hard. Finish things up here well.
Are you sure?
Is it for sure this time?
I wasn't the one who saw it, so it's hard to say.
Our classmate, Jang Hye Rin, has a sister who attended the same university as your sister.
It seems she heard it somewhere.
She said she clearly heard the name Goo Eun Jo.
Okay. I understand, Unni. I'm hanging up.
I'll call you later.
The person named Goo Eun Jo isn't a woman?
No. I'm Goo Eun Jo.
Your name is really Goo Eun Jo?
Yes, that's what I said.
Look, this is my gown. "Goo Eun Jo". See?
Goo Eun Jo
All right. Sorry for the trouble.
Oppa.
Yes?
Oppa, perhaps...
Did you make some promise with Unni?
It's okay. Tell me.
When I asked to start over like to the first day you came to our house
and you accepted without saying anything,
I already knew that you and I weren't thinking about the same thing.
Is there some promise between you two?
Yes.
But...
why didn't you tell me from the start when I asked to start over?
Because I had to think.
About what?
In her letter, Eun Jo told me to take care of you.
I wasn't sure what she meant by take care of you.
I kept thinking and thinking, so I couldn't say it.
I wasn't sure if it meant to protect and help you until Eun Jo is back,
- or...
- Oppa.
Stop talking.
You can stop now.
That's enough. I understand now.
Let's find Eun Jo, with our every effort.
Instead of searching separately, let's put together our efforts to find her.
Don't you think that will be better?
Yeah, let's do that.
Oppa, you...
you've just gotten your heart broken by me.
Why don't you have any reaction?
I just dumped you, okay?
Do you think you are handsome or something?
How are you handsome, in any way?
Is there any handsome man who is so cold?
Don't smile.
If you see Unni,
could you leave our house for a bit?
If you leave and we meet again after a while,
you'll seem more like a brother-in-law, right?
Yes, I'll do that.
I miss
Eun Jo.
Yeah, me too.
Hey, why did you ask me to do such a thing?
I'm sorry. You can get off work and go home.
After I get back from the lab, I'll finish things up.
Well, you don't have to do that.
I'm good at organizing data.
So, you can trust me and go home.
Hello?
Yes. This is Jeon Ho Seong from Mi Do Research Lab.
Yes. How have you been?
Yes, Hyo Seon.
Oppa, after meeting with a buyer I stopped by a bookstore for a while.
There's a short article about yeast published in a science magazine.
The contributing writer doesn't have Unni's name,
but no matter how much I think about it, it seems she wrote it.
What is the title of the article? I'll look it up on my cell phone.
Wait a moment, let me take a look at it.
And Oppa, the name of the research lab is the same as the one we went to.
What do you think has happened?
Yes. This is Jeon Ho Seong from Mi Do Research Lab.
Eun Jo!
Eun Jo! Stop right there!
Eun Jo, wait!
Eun Jo!
You...
How could you...?
I missed you so much.
I looked for you
like crazy, you brat.
The fourth thing... What was it?
What?
The words you wanted to say to MMM.
You told me only three of the four things.
You said you would tell me the fourth thing after you return.
You haven't told me yet.
You want to hear it?
I could've died never hearing it.
I thought you got into an accident.
What is the fourth thing?
- What else could it be?
- Say it!
Hurry up and say it!
Say it before we die!
I love you.
You stupid brat.
I said I love you.
What's MMM?
Mi Malo Muchacha. My stupid brat.
Gyeonggi-do Opening Up the Republic of Korea's future
Dae Seong True Winemakers
Certificate of Award
Representative, Goo Eun Jo
Awarded for significant contribution to promoting our culture
Don't you have anything to admit
in front of Dad?
Don't you know what I am asking you to admit?
I...
I missed you.
What about you?
I also...
missed you.
Thank you to the 🦋 After Happily Ever After 🦋 Team
Thank you to Channel Manager: MaryKarmelina
Thank you to segmenters: kitty100, sabrinafair, pilar_velazquez,
Thank you to segmenters, cont:hana_860, c_scott and marykarmelina
Thank you to Korean to English subtitlers: hannalee123, ccxkiu, marykarmelina, and zohra_29
Thank you t Korean to English subtitlers, cont: cgwm808, stars4U, sophie2you, jenarrtee
Thank you to Korean to English subtitlers, cont: myeongchojune_218 297, baritaggie, and bluewind
Thank you to Editor cgwm808, sophie2you (Translation) and bluewind (Translation)
♫ It must be you.  ♫
♫ I cannot be without you.  ♫
♫ Like this for another day, month or year  ♫
♫ I don't mind even if I am hurt.  ♫
♫ I don't mind even if my heart breaks  ♫
♫ because, yes, you are the only one I love. ♫
♫ My bruised heart ♫
♫ is shouting so that ♫
♫ I can find you. ♫
♫ Wherever you are ♫
♫ Can't you hear my voice? ♫
♫ Come to me. ♫